<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YeeHeng</title><link>https://lauyh.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on YeeHeng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© YeeHeng</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:05:33 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lauyh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://lauyh.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 17:05:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lauyh.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am Yee Heng a.k.a Richard, currently working as a Senior Web Developer at Cyber Village Sdn Bhd. My daily routine is developing new API and mobile app based on the requirement from client. The technology stack that I working on are Angular, Ionic, Java Spring and JPA.
I am passionate to explore new technologies and get the hand dirty on trying the new stuff.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Machine Learning</title><link>https://lauyh.github.io/posts/intro-ml/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:05:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lauyh.github.io/posts/intro-ml/</guid><description>Introduction Academic View Machine Learning(ML) defined as a machine learns whenever it changes its structure, program, or data in such a manner that its expected future performance improves (Nilsson, 2005). While J.D. Kelleher and Tierney, (2018) viewed ML as a field of computer science that focuses developing and evaluating algorithms that can extract useful patterns from datasets. Therefore, the accuracy of the ML model can be improved by continuing collecting new data and feed into the model.</description></item><item><title>Programmer Digest 1</title><link>https://lauyh.github.io/posts/programmer-digest-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:02:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lauyh.github.io/posts/programmer-digest-1/</guid><description>This is a post regarding the summary of
School of Hard Knocks on IT World The harsh reality of “the streets,” the world of professional software develop- ment, requires a set of skills that are not taught or prioritized in formal educa- tion or sometimes are completely missed in self-teaching. New software developers tend to either care about theory or to completely ignore it. You’ll find a middle point eventually, but achieving that can be accel- erated with a certain perspective.</description></item></channel></rss>